{
    "subject": "resource/Michael_D._Sallah",
    "predicate": "ontology/abstract",
    "object": "Michael D. Sallah is a Pulitzer Prize- winning American investigative reporter.",
    "human_readable": "Michael D. Sallah is a Pulitzer Prize-winning American investigative reporter.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.8755913376808167,
            "question": "Is Michael D. Sallah American?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7290927171707153,
            "question": "What prestigious award has Michael D. Sallah won?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6887440085411072,
            "question": "What is Michael D. Sallah known for?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6399083137512207,
            "question": "What type of reporting is Michael D. Sallah known for?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5903763771057129,
            "question": "What nationality is Michael D. Sallah?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5808932781219482,
            "question": "Has Michael D. Sallah received any notable awards?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5776923298835754,
            "question": "What is Michael D. Sallah's area of expertise?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.520069420337677,
            "question": "What is the name of Michael D. Sallah's profession?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.4668515920639038,
            "question": "Where does Michael D. Sallah originate from?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.46506500244140625,
            "question": "In what field does Michael D. Sallah work?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Michael D. Sallah is a Pulitzer Prize-winning American investigative reporter.",
            "html": "dbpedia_2028_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Where does Michael D. Sallah originate from?",
            "html": "dbpedia_2028_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What is the name of Michael D. Sallah's profession?",
            "html": "dbpedia_2028_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What is Michael D. Sallah's area of expertise?",
            "html": "dbpedia_2028_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2028_110.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2028_112.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2028_25.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2028_26.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2028_27.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2028_29.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2028_43.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2028_6.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2028_73.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2028_8.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n```  \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "Here is the structured JSON format containing the evaluation of the triple:\n\n```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe reason for this answer is that the documents contain information about Michael D. Sallah being a Pulitzer Prize-winning journalist, which supports the statement that he is a Pulitzer Prize-winning American investigative reporter."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n```\n\nThe information provided across the documents supports that Michael D. Sallah is indeed a Pulitzer Prize-winning journalist who specializes in investigative reporting. The documents mention his work at various newspapers, his role as an editor, and his receipt of multiple Pulitzer Prizes for Investigative Reporting, which aligns with the statement that he is \"a Pulitzer Prize-winning American investigative reporter.\""
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "The Least Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}